因此，让我们将这一点做得更丰富。
So let's make this even a little
bit nicer developer experience.
如果这是我的特殊容器，我就会这样做。
This is what I would do if this
was my particular container.
我可能会写一个不同的 dev.docker 文件
I'd probably write a different
dev.docker file but
让我们直接修改这个
let's just modify this one directly.
我们要做的是
What we're gonna do here is
在这里我们会说
under here we're gonna say
RUN npm 安装 -全局。
RUN npm install --global.
或者我是懒惰的所以我只能说 npm i -g， Nodemon
Or I'm lazy, so
I'll just say npm i -g, Nodemon.
我听到人们说这一百万种不同的方式，没有魔鬼，没有魔鬼。
And I've heard people say this a million
different ways, no demon, no demon.
我要和你一起去
I'm gonna go with nodemon.
所以你要怎么说那是魔鬼
So it's up to you how you
wanna say that nodemon.
这基本上是一个档案观看者会研究你的
This basically is a file
watcher that will research your
节点服务器每次看到文件更改的情况。
node server every single time
that it sees a file change.
所以我要把它安装在这里。
So makes it really nice to developers So
I'm gonna install that up here.
然后在这里，而不是说节点，我要说的是， nodemon。
And then down here, instead of
saying node, I'm gonna say, nodemon.
这将会使您体验到非常好的开发者体验
And this will make a really
nice developer experience so
我们就可以去写我们的服务器了
we can just be going and
writing our server.
然后每当我们更改文件时，我们就会单击 " 保存 " 和 "
And then every time that we change
our file, we'll click save and
一切都会好的现在我们有了
everything will just work So
right now, we have
以停止所有这些内容，然后在每次更改文件时重新启动它。
to stop all this stuff and then restart it
every single time that we change a file.
我觉得这很不好玩
I would say that's unfun.
所以现在我们有了新恶魔我们可以做得非常快因为我不需要
So now with nodemon, we can make this
really fast because I won't have to
每次对文件进行更改时，重新启动容器。
restart the container every single time
that we make our change to the files.
既然我们已经完成了保存文档的程序
So now that we've done that
we save to docker file,
我们会说码头的组成
we're gonna say docker-compose up.
它应该穿过并重建我们的容器。
It should go through and
rebuild our container.
它看起来不像是重建了我们的容器
It doesn't look like it
actually rebuilt our container,
我们要自己做吗
do we need to do it ourselves?
我可能改错了，我改错了。
I might be modifying the wrong one,
I am, I modified the wrong one.
当您有 19 个 Docker 文件时，将到期。
It's due when you have 19 Docker files.
好吧对不起
All right, sorry.
加入您的网络 Docker 文件。
So come into your networking Docker file.
我要在这做
I'm gonna do that up here.
一样的
Same thing.
RUN npm i -g nodemon ，然后在此处， nodemon。
RUN npm i -g nodemon, and
then down here, nodemon.
所以我们每次都能重新启动我们的开发环境
So that we can restart our development
environment every single time that we
保存文件。
save a file.
好了阻止我们的服务器
Okay, stop our server.
你可以看到它正在为我们创造网络，这很棒。
You can see that it's creating networks
on the fly for us, which is nice.
然后我们就会重新开始码头
And then here we'll
restart docker-compose up.
所以一切都应该在这里工作
So everything should
be still working here.
在这里，这是一个网络，而不是说成功:
And then here, this is a networking,
so instead of saying success: true,
也许我们会说成功是假的
maybe we're gonna say success: false
我不确定这是否最终重建了它，让我们看看。
And I'm not sure this actually ended
up rebuilding it, let's check.
是啊不是
Yeah, it didn't.
那为什么呢
So why is that?
有什么地方可以重建吗
Is there somewhere I can force rebuild?
好的我们来吧
Yeah, let's do that.
好了我们要做的是我们要说的是 Docker
Okay, so what we're gonna do,
is we're gonna say docker-compose
up -build ，因为我们知道修改了 Docker 文件。
up --build because we know
we modified our Docker file.
它会迫使它为我们建造一个网络容器。
It's gonna force it to build
the web container for us.
通常，您不会非常修改 Docker 文件。
Typically, you're not modifying
your Docker file very much.
通常编写 Docker 文件和
Usually you write your Docker file and
那就需要几个月才能再修改
then it's a couple of months before
you have to go modify it again.
一旦建成，这将为我们工作。
And then once this is built
this will work for us.
好了这就在这里说假话
Okay, so, now, this is saying false here.
所以不需要做整首歌和舞蹈对吧我们通常要
So instead of having to do that whole song
and dance, right, typically we'd have to
stop docker-compose， docker-compose up， build， wait for
stop docker-compose,
docker-compose up, build, wait for
Docker 文件将在每次查看更改时再次构建。
the Docker file to build again every
single time that we wanna see a change.
理论上如果我回来的话
Now, in theory, if I come back.
上面说现在是假的
It says false right now right there.
如果我说真的，我去看看，它应该告诉我它可能重启了。
If I say true, and I go look here,
it should tell me that it restarted maybe.
无论如何现在都是真的了
Well, in any case, it's true now.
这样我们就能更快地迭代
So now this allows us to
more rapidly iterate,
你就像布莱恩 - 伊桑，那是 100% 的真实情况。
So you can be like brianIsCool,
and that's 100% true.
我现在可以刷新了，布莱恩 - 伊斯酷: 真的。
And I could refresh now,
brianIsCool: true.
很酷吧
Very cool, right?
跟我一样
Just like me.
再一次，这是一种非常好的表面划伤。
Again, this is a very kind
of scratching the surface.
你能用这个做更多的工作
There's a lot more you can do with this.
让我们在这里做点有趣的事情。
Let's actually do something
a little bit fun here as well.
所以我要再停一次再等这个
So I'm gonna stop this again,
wait for this to stop.
关于 Docker 的最酷的事就是如果你想模拟
The cool thing about docker compose
is if you wanna simulate like running
多个服务器，以确保所有操作都正常工作，
multiple servers at the same to make sure
that everything is working correctly,
我们可以说 docker-compose up ，然后我可以说 --scale web=10.
we can say docker-compose up and
then I can say --scale web=10.
而不是只启动一个像以前一样的网络容器
Instead of starting just one web container
which is what it was doing before,
现在它会启动十个网络容器
now it's gonna start ten web containers.
我都不知道为什么
I don't even know why,
可能是因为他们都在听同样的港口
it's probably because they're
all listening to the same ports.
是的他们都想绑定到同一个港口
Yes, they're all trying
to bind to the same port.
是啊所以我们得过去
Yeah, and so we have to go through and
就像一种更聪明的循环法对不同的端口进行绑定。
have like a smarter like round-robin
way of binding to different ports.
让你看看这到底是怎么工作的
Just to show you how this
actually would work, let's just.
如果我摆脱了这就意味着它不再工作了
If I just got rid of this which
means it wouldn't work anymore, but
它就会启动
it would start up.
好了好了
There you go.
然后它就会启动这些不同的容器。
So then it's gonna go and start these
various different containers up.
你可以在这里看到我有一大堆从这里飞过来的
And you can see here now I have a bunch
of all these different logs flown in from
同一 Web 容器的七个不同版本。
seven different versions
of the same web container.
因此，如果您对端口和端口的绑定变得更加智慧，
So if you're a bit smarter about
how you're binding into ports and
你的倾听
how you're listening,
你可能得在它前面有某种负载均衡器
you probably have to have some sort
of like load balancer in front of it.
这样你就能像现在的那种人一样
So you could do that with like nginx,
you could do with like traffic,
有一堆能为你做的事情
there is a bunch of things
that will do it for you.
然后，它将在所有不同的容器之间进行负载均衡。
And then it would load balance between
all your various different containers.
这比我现在想和 Docker 创作的要多了很多
That's a lot more involved than I wanna
get right now with Docker compose, but
这里的一切都是绝对可能的
all things are definitely possible here.
很酷的是我们把我们的服务推广到 10 个不同的
And it's pretty cool that we just
scaled out our service to ten different
就像那样只为了好玩
containers just like that, just for fun.
好的
Okay, cool.
嗯， ha_proxy 也能在这里工作。
Yeah, ha_proxy would work for
here as well.